http://www.novabiotech.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

About Us
Welcome to Nova Biotech's Online Store!
Nova Biotech provides service and sales support for Uv/Vis Spectrophotometers, Spectrofluorometers, Microplate Readers, FTIR, PCR, HPLC, FPLC and Temperature Control instruments across the U.S. and Canada and beyond.
In addition, we are the authorized sales and service providers for Gilford and Unico spectrophotometers. Our offices and depot repair facilities are located in Southern California near San Diego. Our Field Service Engineers located across the country provide local on-site service. We have more than 25 years of experience servicing biotech and biomedical instrumentation.
More >>>
Account Services
Account Information
"My Account" Benifits
By creating an account at Nova Biotech you will be able to place your orders quickly, check the status of your orders, view all of your previous orders, and sign up to recieve product updates.
Secured SSL ConnectionWhile logged in, your data is sent via an SSL connection and protected by encryption, a mechanism that prevents eavesdropping and tampering with any transmitted data. All data sent to Nova Biotech, such as credit card numbers and other private information, are kept confidential and secure.
Visitors Cart / Members Cart
Visitors CartEvery visitor to our online shop will be given a 'Visitors Cart'. This allows the visitor to store their products in a temporary shopping cart. Once the visitor leaves the online shop, so will the contents of their shopping cart.
Members CartEvery member to our online shop that logs in is given a 'Members Cart'. This allows the member to add products to their shopping cart, and come back at a later date to finalize their checkout. All products remain in their shopping cart until the member has
checked them out, or removed the products themselves.
InfoIf a member adds products to their 'Visitors Cart' and decides to log in to the online shop to use their 'Members Cart', the contents of their 'Visitors Cart' will merge with their 'Members Cart' contents automatically.
Cookie Privacy and Security
Cookies on this site are used for your security and convenience. You do not need to enable cookies to browse this site, but, if you want to take advantage of our member services or shop online, cookies must be allowed to securely identify you and your requests.
If cookies cannot be enabled in your browser, please contact us to complete your request offline.Nova Biotech does not sell, trade or rent information that you provide to us to any third party. Privacy Policy.
Shop with Confidence
With over 25 years of experience servicing laboratory instrument and our Nationwide coverage you can count on us to meet all of your instrument needs.
Information
Create Account
Log In
Advanced Search
Site Map
Shipping & Returns
Privacy Notice
Contact Us
Request Service
Lab Equipment ServiceFluorometerGilfordKontron (Uvikon)FPLCGE / Amersham / PharmaciaHPLCAgilentPCRABIABI / Perkin ElmerBio Rad (MJ Research)EppendorfStratagenePlate ReaderABIBio-TekBiologBMGMolecular DevicesPerception Biosystems (ABI)TecanVictor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)SpectrophotometerAgilentAgilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)BeckmanBio RadBiochromEppendorfGEGilfordHitachiKontron (Uvikon)Perkin ElmerPharmacia (Amersham)ShimadzuSpectronicThermoUnicoUvikonVarian - AgilentLab Equipment CalibrationFluorometerGilfordKontron (Uvikon)FPLCGE / Amersham / PharmaciaHPLCAgilentPCRABIABI / Perkin ElmerBio Rad (MJ Research)EppendorfStratagenePlate ReaderABIBio-TekBiologBMGMolecular DevicesPerception Biosystems (ABI)TecanVictor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)SpectrophotometerAgilentAgilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)BeckmanBio RadBiochromEppendorfGEGilfordHitachiKontron (Uvikon)Perkin ElmerPharmacia (Amersham)ShimadzuSpectronicThermoUnicoUvikonVarian - AgilentLab Equipment RepairsFluorometerGilfordKontron (Uvikon)FPLCGE / Amersham / PharmaciaHPLCAgilentPCRABIABI / Perkin ElmerBio Rad (MJ Research)EppendorfStratagenePlate ReaderABIBio-TekBiologBMGMolecular DevicesPerception Biosystems (ABI)TecanVictor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)SpectrophotometerAgilentAgilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)BeckmanBio RadBiochromEppendorfGEGilfordHitachiKontron (Uvikon)Perkin ElmerPharmacia (Amersham)ShimadzuSpectronicThermoUnicoUvikonVarian - Agilent
Scientific EquipmentNew / Used / Parts
Micro Plate Readers
Refurbished Instruments
Lab Equipment Service
Fluorometer
Gilford
Kontron (Uvikon)
FPLC
GE / Amersham / Pharmacia
HPLC
Agilent
PCR
ABI
ABI / Perkin Elmer
Bio Rad (MJ Research)
Eppendorf
Stratagene
Plate Reader
ABI
Bio-Tek
Biolog
BMG
Molecular Devices
Perception Biosystems (ABI)
Tecan
Victor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)
Spectrophotometer
Agilent
Agilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)
Beckman
Bio Rad
Biochrom
Eppendorf
GE
Gilford
Hitachi
Kontron (Uvikon)
Perkin Elmer
Pharmacia (Amersham)
Shimadzu
Spectronic
Thermo
Unico
Uvikon
Varian - Agilent
Lab Equipment Calibration
Fluorometer
Gilford
Kontron (Uvikon)
FPLC
GE / Amersham / Pharmacia
HPLC
Agilent
PCR
ABI
ABI / Perkin Elmer
Bio Rad (MJ Research)
Eppendorf
Stratagene
Plate Reader
ABI
Bio-Tek
Biolog
BMG
Molecular Devices
Perception Biosystems (ABI)
Tecan
Victor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)
Spectrophotometer
Agilent
Agilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)
Beckman
Bio Rad
Biochrom
Eppendorf
GE
Gilford
Hitachi
Kontron (Uvikon)
Perkin Elmer
Pharmacia (Amersham)
Shimadzu
Spectronic
Thermo
Unico
Uvikon
Varian - Agilent
Lab Equipment Repairs
Fluorometer
Gilford
Kontron (Uvikon)
FPLC
GE / Amersham / Pharmacia
HPLC
Agilent
PCR
ABI
ABI / Perkin Elmer
Bio Rad (MJ Research)
Eppendorf
Stratagene
Plate Reader
ABI
Bio-Tek
Biolog
BMG
Molecular Devices
Perception Biosystems (ABI)
Tecan
Victor Wallac (Perkin Elmer)
Spectrophotometer
Agilent
Agilent / Hewlett Packard (HP)
Beckman
Bio Rad
Biochrom
Eppendorf
GE
Gilford
Hitachi
Kontron (Uvikon)
Perkin Elmer
Pharmacia (Amersham)
Shimadzu
Spectronic
Thermo
Unico
Uvikon
Varian - Agilent
Spectrophotometers
New
SLM/Aminco
Spectronic (B&L)
UNICO
Uvikon (Kontron / Bio Tek / Seco
Varian / Cary
Spectrofluorometer Lamps
Aminco Bowman / SLM
AVIV
BAS
Beckman / Altex
Nova Biotech’s Privacy Policy
This is the web site of Nova Biotech, a division of Integrated Medical Maintenance Management, Inc. a California company. Our business mailing address is 1906 Grove Road, El Cajon, CA 92020. We can be reached by e mail at info@novabiotech.com. Or you can reach us by telephone at 619-579-0077, or by fax at 619-579-0061.
At Nova Biotech, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Nova Biotech does not sell, trade or rent information that you provide to us to any third party. For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name, but not the e mail address (where possible). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.
If you do not want to receive e mail from us, please let us know by writing to us at the above address and telling us that you do not want to receive e mail from our company. If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online or in person
may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. They also may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by writing to us at the above address. Please provide us with your correct phone number.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Thank you for your business and your interest in our privacy policy.
Information
Lab Equipment Parts
Instrument Calibration
Lab Equipment Repairs
Lab Equipment Maintenance
Instrument Lamp Replacement Information
Cuvette Comparisons, Information and Tips
New and Used Scientific Equipment
1. Spectronic 21 Spectrophotometer...
2. UV Quartz, Open Top Lid...
3. Beckman DU-520, DU 530...
4. Lamp, Visible Agilent-Stratagene...
Important Links
Site Map
Conditions of Use
Privacy Notice
Contact InformationPhone: 619.579.0077Fax: 619.579.0061Email: info@NovaBiotech.com
InformationAbout UsSite MapCuvette ComparisonsLamp Replacement GuideNewsletter Unsubscribe
Customer SupportContact UsShipping & ReturnsPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseMy AccountUseful Links My Account
